‌

['%3e%3ccircle cx='8.152' cy='8.152' r='8.152'/%3e%3cpath d='M19.565 19.565l-5.652-5.652'/%3e%3c/g%3e%3c/svg%3e "Search Icon")](https://www.sonyliv.com/)

SonyLIV

PRIVACY POLICY
--------------

### 1\. APPLICABILITY OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy is applicable to personally identifiable information (hereinafter referred to as "Personal Data" and detailed below) collected, processed, stored and used by Sony Pictures Networks India Private Limited having its registered office at Interface Building 7, Floor 45, Malad (West), Mumbai – 400064, India ("SPN") either through its owned, controlled and operated website located at**[http://www.sonyliv.com](https://www.sonyliv.com/)**and/or app named SonyLIV (collectively and individually referred to as "SonyLIV"), in connection with individual Users' ("User", "You", or "Your") access to or use of SonyLIV services. SonyLIV is available on various platforms and devices like mobile phones, tablets, smart televisions, set top boxes and various other devices on which SonyLIV is embedded or otherwise made available.

### 2\. ACCEPTANCE OF THE TERMS OF THIS POLICY

i. This Privacy Policy should be read in conjunction with the Terms of Use and the Cookie Policy.  
ii. By using SonyLIV, You agree to SPN's terms of processing Your Personal Data which You provide to SPN in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  
iii. Please also note that SonyLIV may contain links to third-party websites, platforms or applications not owned, operated or controlled by SPN. SPN is not responsible for the privacy practices of or for the Personal Data processed by such third-party websites, platforms or applications that You may visit.  
iv. The Personal Data that such third-party websites, platforms or applications collect directly from You (for example, payment processing) is subject to such third-party website, platform or application's privacy practices. Privacy choices You may make on the third-party websites, platforms or applications will not apply to SPN or SPN's processing of the Personal Data as per this Privacy Policy applications.  
v. SPN encourages You to be aware of the privacy practices of such other websites, platforms or applications that You may choose to access from SonyLIV and that may collect Your Personal Data.

### 3\. ACCESS TO SERVICES OF SONYLIV

The access to complete content and services on SonyLIV is only available on a subscription basis and to Users who are above the age of 18 years. SPN may provide children content or content suitable for individuals below the age of 18 years on SonyLIV but the same shall only be accessible through the profile of a parent or legal guardian who is an adult.

### 4\. DEFINITION OF PERSONAL DATA

"Personal Data" means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person. An identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person. When anonymous information is directly or indirectly associated with personal data, the resulting information also is treated as personal data.  
  
To access SonyLIV, SPN requires You to provide Your Personal Data since SPN cannot identify You by a pseudonym or through anonymous data. SPN may collect anonymized data from You based on certain activity You perform on SonyLIV for analytics and statistical purposes. Such anonymized data will not be associated with Your Personal Data and will not be applicable under this Privacy Policy.

### 5\. COLLECTION OF PERSONAL DATA

SPN may collect the following Personal Data from You:  
**5.1 Information You Provide to SPN  
****A.**At the time of Registration and Sign Up  
To use SonyLIV and the services it offers, Users must register and create an account ("Account"). Creating the Account may require the User to provide the following Personal Data associated with the User, including but not limited to:  
i. Mobile number  
ii. E-mail address  
iii. Location (IP, Lat-Long, Country Code)  
  
**B.**At the time of Account and Profile Creation  
To use SonyLIV and the services it offers, Users must register and create an account ("Account"). Creating the Account may require the User to provide the following Personal Data associated with the User, including but not limited to:  
i. Name  
ii. Profile name  
  
**C.**At the time of using coupon codes  
You may also subscribe to SonyLIV by using an activation or subscription codes or coupon provided by SPN or its commercial associates authorized to issue codes or coupons. SPN may store details related to codes or coupons You use including but not limited to:  
i. Session ID  
ii. IP address  
iii. Device ID  
iv. Order ID  
**5.2 Additional Personal Data provided by You Voluntarily  
**If You send any correspondences, such as emails or letters including data subject requests to SPN, or if other users or third parties send Personal Data about Your activities or postings on SonyLIV to SPN, then SPN may collect and store such Personal Data. SPN may collect additional Personal Data at other times, including but not limited to, when You provide feedback, when You change Your content or email preferences etc. This Personal Data includes the information You may share with SPN during such correspondence like Your name, e-mail id, mobile number, city, country, etc.  
  
The additional Personal Data mentioned above is collected solely for the purpose of communicating with the User regarding the SonyLIV services, processing the feedback received, and conducting surveys to implement suggestions, processing and implementing change requests, data subject requests and enriching the overall user experience. Users will be asked to provide their consent in case the above-mentioned Personal Data is processed for any purpose other than those detailed above.  

### 5.3 Personal Data automatically collected while browsing or navigating through SonyLIV

A. Throughout Your use of SonyLIV, SPN may use a variety of technologies that automatically or passively collect Personal Data with respect to how SonyLIV is accessed and used by You ("Usage Information").  
Usage Information may consist, inter alia, of the following data about Your visit, usage of services and consumption of content on SonyLIV:i. Content viewed  
ii. Types of content viewed  
iii. Date and time of view  
iv. Content added to ‘My List'  
v. Number of times You visited SonyLIV in a specific duration of time  
vi. Number of page views  
vii. Type of computer operating system including the type of internet browser and internet service provider.  
viii. Quality of content streaming at the time of video playout  
ix. Number of concurrent sessions  
Usage Information is generally of a nature which is non-identifiable of a natural person (for example aggregate analytics). However, in order to process such Usage Information and to make it feasible for SPN's legitimate business interests, SPN may associate the Usage Information with other information collected from You and such combination may be treated as Personal Data.  
B. SPN may also collect Your IP address from Your computer, mobile or any other device on which You access SonyLIV. An "IP address" is an identifying number for network hardware connected to a network. It helps to recognize the location of the User.  
  
SPN uses IP address for the following purposes:i. Determining Your geographic location, and provide content available in the said geographic location;  
ii. Processing Your registration and payments;  
iii. To enable processing of coupons or vouchers for subscription offers; and  
iv. To detect and monitor any fraudulent activity.  
  
C. SPN may collect unique identifier from Your device. It is a number that is automatically assigned to Your device when You access SonyLIV, use its services and stream content therefrom, and SPN's systems will identify Your device by this number ("Device Identifier").  
If collected, these Device Identifiers will be used for the following purposes:i. Providing the User with SonyLIV content and services based on the User's location;  
ii. To enable processing of coupons/vouchers for subscription offers;  
iii. Identifying the User when he/she accesses or downloads SonyLIV; and  
iv. Measuring the User behavior in terms of user interface, clicks, response etc.  
  
D. SPN may also have integrations of SonyLIV with some third-party service providers who may, on SPN's instructions, collect the Device Identifier or create their own unique Device Identifier including but not limited to:i. Clevertap ID to provide You with push notifications;  
ii. CP Customer ID to identify unique user;  
iii. GA ID to help SPN derive analytical insights;  
iv. Charged ID for transaction purposes;  
v. Profile ID assigned to each profile created by You for mapping the Content; and  
vi. Order ID for unique user making a subscription on SonyLIV.  
E. Cookies  
To improve Your experience on SonyLIV, SPN collects, uses and stores cookies. Cookies are files that web servers place on Your device to provide You with a seamless interaction with the web and application platforms. Some of these cookies are mandatory for functioning of SonyLIV while some cookies are used to track Your behavior on SonyLIV for an enhanced experience. SPN will seek Your consent before using any cookies which are not mandatory in nature. For more information about the cookies SPN uses, please refer to SPN's Cookie Policy.  
  
F. SPN also uses asynchronous technology for the purpose of building web applications and providing optimized performance of SonyLIV in terms of fetching, loading and refreshing the content. SPN does not pass any Usage Information or Personal Data to any of these technology providers through use of their technology or otherwise.  
  
G. For the smooth functioning of SonyLIV, SPN may also use an analytics service provider. Such service providers may use an analytics tool. Analytics tools use cookies, text files, SDKs, APIs, etc. that are stored on Your device and allow an analysis of Your use of SonyLIV. The information generated by the cookies about Your use of SonyLIV, including the IP address, may be transferred to and stored on a server of such analytics service provider engaged by SPN, which may not be located within the EU, EEA and UK and who may use such information, to analyze Your use of SonyLIV, to create reports about the activities and to provide further services associated with the use of SonyLIV to SPN. Furthermore, it may transfer such information generated to third parties, to the extent legally required or permitted or if such third parties process the information on behalf of the analytics service providers. You will be asked to provide Your consent for such storage and transfer of Your Personal Data to the third parties which may or may not be located within the territory from which You are accessing SonyLIV.  
  
H.**In App Permissions**  
To provide You with certain features and to improve Your experience on the application of SonyLIV, SPN asks You for the following in app permissions:i. Microphone  
ii. Gallery  
iii. Phone/SMS  
iv. Camera  
v. In APP purchases  
vi. Bluetooth  
SPN will seek Your consent before using any permissions which are not mandatory in nature. The use of microphone and phone/SMS are essential to use audio for audio searching and sending an OTP (one -time-password) for Your authentication purposes for registration and/or subscription of SonyLIV, respectively.  

### 5.4. Inferred information through usage and log data

SPN may track certain information about You, in an anonymized manner, based upon Your behavior while using SonyLIV for below mentioned purposes of analytics and statistical insights:i. To perform analytics and conduct customer research, to determine Your interest, for identifying content that generate sales and to analyze traffic patterns;  
ii. To study traffic patterns to improve website performance, to customize user experience, and to better match users' interests and preferences;  
iii. Keep track of preferences You specify while You are using SonyLIV content or services;  
iv. Capturing video playback features and working on SonyLIV;  
v. Capturing user behavior for measuring quality specifications of SonyLIV;  
vi. Keeping track of multiple profiles created by You.

### 5.5. Third Party Payment Gateway – Financial Information

SonyLIV uses third-party payment gateways to process payments made on SonyLIV. SPN will provide You with a confirmation of having received payments against Your subscription Account, only once SPN receives such confirmation from the concerned third-party payment gateway service providers. The third-party payment gateway service providers may require certain financial information including Your credit card, debit card, mobile number or other bank account information. Other than providing a confirmation upon receipt of payment against a subscription Account, SPN disclaims all liabilities in relation to Your payment processing by such third-party payment gateway service providers and the collection and processing of any Personal Data provided by You to such third-party payment gateway service providers. While using such third-party payment gateways to make payments to SPN, You will be required to accept the terms of use and privacy policies of such third-party payment gateway service providers. SPN requests You to familiarize with the terms of use and privacy policies of the respective third-party payment gateway service providers before using such service. You hereby agree and acknowledge that SPN shall not be liable and in no way, be held responsible for any losses whatsoever, whether direct, indirect, incidental or consequential, including without limitation any losses due to online fraud arising from Your use of such payment gateways. In case of any issues or complaints with respect to the processing of Your payments in relation to SonyLIV, You may file a complaint with the concerned third-party payment gateways directly for redressal.  
In case of recurring payments, the amount will be automatically deducted from the bank account, debit or credit card the details of which You may have provided. The subscription amount will automatically get deducted until You otherwise opt to cancel the auto debit by visiting SonyLIV and cancelling subscription in Your Account.  
SPN never asks for password, financial details or any additional personal data without highlighting the purpose of collecting the same.

### 6\. PURPOSE OF COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA

SPN may use the Personal Data collected for the following purposes:i. process Your registration on SonyLIV;  
ii. determine Your geographic location and provide content available in the said territory;  
iii. enable You to visit SonyLIV and enjoy more seamless visits to SonyLIV;  
iv. enable You to use and receive the services offered on SonyLIV including e-mail communications informing You about the services and content provided through SonyLIV;  
v. enable processing of coupons or vouchers for subscription  
vi. contact You about Your Account and in connection with any services or content support, feedback through SonyLIV;  
vii. improve and enhance SonyLIV usage experience according to Your preferences;  
viii. increasing security measures to keep Your data safe by preventing, detecting and investigating potentially prohibited or illegal activities;  
ix. support security measures, such as requiring re-login into SonyLIV after a certain amount of time has elapsed;  
x. analyzing the User behavior to generate analytical insights and provide enhanced SonyLIV services;  
xi. creating custom reports on payment/redemption against each device make, model, serial number;  
xii. notify You about changes in the services offered by SonyLIV or changes in this Privacy Policy; and  
xiii. other purposes specifically disclosed to You prior to the collection of Your Personal Data or otherwise with Your consent.If SPN wishes to collect and process Your Personal Data for purposes other than those mentioned above, SPN shall seek a specific consent from You prior to collecting and processing Your Personal Data for such additional purposes unless this falls within legitimate business interest for processing as explained in paragraph 7 below.

### 7\. PROCESSING OF PERSONAL DATA COLLECTED

SPN processes Your Personal Data for the purposes detailed hereunder, basis the following lawful basis under GDPR: (i) obtaining explicit consent from You for processing Your Personal Data; (ii) where it is necessary for SPN to undertake its legal obligations; (iii) SPN's exercise of its rights under a contract with You; or (iv) processing of Personal Data for legitimate interests where processing is not necessary to meet contractual obligations, but is necessary to provide You with services and content of SonyLIV.

### 8\. SHARING AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL DATA

SPN may share Personal Data with the following parties:

### 8.1. Service providers providing services on SPN's behalf

SPN may, from time to time, employ third-party service providers to perform certain functions on SPN's behalf, such as hosting or operation of SonyLIV, hosting the Personal Data, e-mails, messages or other communications, and providing data analysis services etc. within or outside Your country. Wherever Your Personal Data is transferred, stored or processed, SPN will take reasonable steps to safeguard the privacy of Your Personal Data. Any Personal Data shall be disclosed to such third-party service providers only after ensuring contractual protection of Your Personal Data, including that such third-party service providers implement adequate technical measures to safeguard Your Personal Data. These third-party service providers are prohibited from using Your Personal Data for purposes other than those specified in Paragraph 6 above or required by law.

### 8.2. Affiliates of SPN and Business Transfers

SPN operates globally and it may transfer Your Personal Data to SPN's affiliated companies primarily for business and operational purposes.  
SPN or any of its businesses, including SonyLIV, may be acquired or merged or de-merged or spun-off or may be subject to any other transactions wherein SPN may no longer remain the controller or processor of Your Personal Data. In such cases, where any such transaction takes place which covers Your Personal Data, Your Personal Data shall be transferred as part of such transaction. Such transfer of Your Personal Data will without any further notice to the Users and by using SonyLIV, You hereby acknowledge and agree that this Privacy Policy will serve as notice enough for any such transfer.

### 8.3. Disclosures required under laws and regulations

SPN may transfer and disclose Your Personal Data to: i. comply with a requirement or an obligation under a law or regulation when SPN in good faith believes that such disclosure is required under such law or regulation;  
ii. to government and regulatory authorities at their request or order;  
iii. to verify or enforce SonyLIV's Privacy Policy, Terms of Use, Cookie Policy or other applicable policies;  
iv. to protect the rights, property, safety, or security of third parties, users or the public or in response to a similar emergency.

### 9\. YOUR CONTROLS AND CHOICES

### 9.1. Accessing and rectifying your Personal Data

When You use SonyLIV, SPN makes reasonable efforts to provide You with Your right to access Your Personal Data and further upholding the accuracy of the Personal Data by providing You with a fairly simple functionality within SonyLIV for rectifying Your Personal Data You may have provided. For example, You can easily access or edit Your Account information (Name, Profile Name) through the "MY ACCOUNT" section available on SonyLIV.

### 9.2. Data Portability

You may request copies, in a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format, of the Personal Data that You provided to SPN, wherever feasible. Alternatively, You may request for Your Personal Data to be transmitted to another service provider (where technically feasible) directly by SPN.

### 9.3. Data Retention and Erasure

SPN retains Your Personal Data for legitimate business interests and until SPN requires such Personal Data for the purposes for which the same has been collected as specified in Paragraphs 6 and 7. SPN may also need to retain Your Personal Data for SPN to comply with legal obligations as specified in Paragraph 8. If You no longer want SPN to use Your Personal Data, then You can request that SPN erases Your Personal Data. Do note that if You request for the erasure of Your Personal Data, SPN may retain some of the Personal Data as may be required for the following purposes:  
i. a unique identifier used for registration purposes such as e-mail or mobile number to detect for any fraudulent activity such as obtaining free consecutive trial offers;  
ii. retention and use of Your Personal Data as necessary for SPN's legitimate business interests, such as fraud detection and prevention and enhancing safety;  
iii. retention and use of Your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with SPN's legal obligations (specified above). For example, SPN may keep some of Your Personal Data for tax, legal reporting and auditing obligations;  
iv. Personal Data You share with SPN (e.g. comments, complaints, feedback etc.) maybe retained for legitimate purposes, even after Your Account or subscription is cancelled, suspended, terminated or withdrawn; and  
v. Because of the way SPN maintains certain services, after You delete Your Personal Data, residual copies of such Personal Data, it may take some time before these are deleted from SPN's active servers and may remain in SPN's backup systems.  

You should be aware that it may not be possible to completely remove or delete all Your Personal Data from SPN's databases to effect any opt-out preferences You have made due to technical concerns with data backup and contingency support.  
Your request for deletion, or modification of Your Personal Data shall be subject to the following:  
i. where You have shared Your Personal Data, that You wish to request for deletion or modification, directly with a third party vendor, You shall request such third party vendor for deletion or modification of Your Personal Data. SPN shall not be responsible for the deletion or modification of such Personal Data as a data controller; and  
ii. in case the Personal Data that You request for deletion or modification has been collected and used only by SPN and SPN's appointed and contracted processors and contractors, SPN shall be responsible for the deletion or modification of the Personal Data requested subject to the data retention conditions stipulated in this Privacy Policy.  
Do note that if You have multiple accounts with SonyLIV, then You will have to raise separate requests for deletion or modification of Your Personal Data for each of the Accounts, along with the associated email IDs or phone numbers or provide SPN with any unique identifiers as may be required for identifying Your Personal Data in SPN's systems.

### 9.4. Objection and Restriction of Processing

Where there is a lawful basis for processing Your Personal Data and such processing falls within SPN's legitimate interest like, without limitation, Device ID, IP Address, geo-location, User ID, or where You have reasons to believe that the Personal Data being processed by SPN is inaccurate, unlawful or is no longer required to be processed by SPN under any lawful basis, You may, at any time, ask SPN to restrict or object the processing of Your Personal Data.

9.5. To send a request for any of the above-mentioned purposes, kindly send an e-mail to SPN's DPO at dpo@setindia.com. SPN may take up to 30 (thirty) days from the date of receipt of request to complete Your requests. However, if the nature of Your request requires significant effort or is time consuming in terms of locating the date or in terms of quantity of data that it relates to, then SPN may ask for an extension of a further 60 (sixty) days by giving a prior notice to You with the reason for the extension.

9.6. SPN shall not charge You for fulfilling any of the above requests. However, if the fulfilment of any such request leads to certain costs being incurred by SPN, then SPN will notify You prior to processing such request.

9.7. SPN advises the Users to identify themselves in their requests to the DPO for exercising any of their rights with respect to their Personal Data. SPN may not be able to process any requests made in the event the User fails to identify themselves or if SPN is unable to authenticate such a User. SPN may also decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, requiring disproportionate effort, jeopardizing the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical or for which access is not otherwise required.

9.8. Please be aware that if You do not allow SPN to collect Personal Data from You, SPN may not be able to deliver certain experiences, features and services to You, and some of SonyLIV's services may not be able to take account of Your interests and preferences. If collection of Personal Data is mandatory, SPN shall inform You at the point of collection so that You can make an informed decision whether You wish to allow the processing of such Personal Data.

### 10\. CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

SonyLIV may, in future, make available content that will apply or be directed at persons less than 18 years of age and such content may be accessed only by via the profile of the parents or legal guardians of the minors. SPN does not intend to collect or knowingly collect Personal Data from minors. SPN does not knowingly permit any person who is under 18 years of age to register with SonyLIV or to provide any other Personal Data. Parents or the legal guardians are advised to monitor the minor's use of SonyLIV, who are accessing the services and content of SonyLIV through the profiles of such parents or legal guardians. It shall be the parent's or legal guardian's responsibility to decide whether or not the use of or access to SonyLIV is suitable for their minor and to monitor the Personal Data of the minor, required for his or her use of or access to SonyLIV and the consents for the same. SonyLIV does provide a functionality of Parental Control for such purposes where You can lock Your profile with the help of a password.  
In the event SPN collects Personal Data of minors, SPN will obtain a parental consent from the minor's parent or legal guardian prior to collection and processing of such Personal Data.

### 11\. SPN'S COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY AND CHOICES

i. SPN respects Your privacy and is committed to protecting the personally identifiable information You provide when You use or access SonyLIV services. SPN takes commercially reasonable and appropriate precautions to protect Your Personal Data from unauthorized disclosure and security breaches.  
ii. You understand that the services offered by SonyLIV are on a subscription basis. SPN may send SMS, e-mail or other notification prior to expiry of Your subscription services to notify you about the last date of Your subscription. For auto renewal subscription, You may receive SMS, E-mail or notification from SPN or SPN's authorized vendor notifying You about the renewal of your subscription pack depending upon the subscription duration and payment preferences You may have chosen at the time of registration and creation of Your Account.  
iii. It is important to let You know that electronic data can be intercepted, corrupted, lost or destroyed. SPN cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any data and consequently Your use of SonyLIV is at Your own risk. SPN is however continuously implementing and updating administrative, technical and physical security measures to help protect Your Personal Data against unauthorized access, loss, destruction, corruption or alteration.  
iv. If You know or have reason to believe that Your account credentials have been lost, stolen, altered, or otherwise compromised or there has been an actual or suspected unauthorized use of Your account, please contact Data Protection Officer (DPO) by email at[dpo@setindia.com](mailto:dpo@setindia.com).

### 12\. NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES AND YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THE PRIVACY POLICY

SPN will update this Privacy Policy from time to time in response to changing legal, regulatory, business or operational requirements or when there is a change or update in the services offered on SonyLIV. SPN will provide notice of any such changes to the Privacy Policy, including when such changes will take effect, in accordance with the applicable law. Your continued use of SonyLIV after any such updates to the Privacy Policy will constitute acknowledgement and acceptance of those changes. If You do not wish to acknowledge or accept any updates to this Privacy Policy, You may cancel Your Account, subscription and use of SonyLIV.

### 13\. CONTACT INFORMATION

i. Processing, usage and storage of Personal Data  
ii. This Privacy Policy  
iii. Exercise of Your rights as a data subject as provided under the applicable law  
iv. Grievances with respect to processing, usage and storage of Your Personal Data  
v. General enquiry/ clarification in relation to the Personal Data  
vi. Suggestions/ feedback related to Privacy Policy and privacy practices  
If You contact SPN with a privacy complaint, it will be assessed with the aim of resolving the issue in a timely and effective manner. Please note that if You contact SPN to assist You in this regard, for Your safety and SonyLIV's, SPN may need to authenticate Your identity before fulfilling Your request.  
In case You require technical support (like subscription related, app functioning related, technical related, payment related, etc.), You may write to SPN at prioritysupport@sonyliv.com.  
SPN will only use Your email id for customer interaction and communication. After your query is resolved, SPN will not share with You information about its services including the SonyLIV, either through mailers or any other form of communication for which You dont provide consent to SPN.  
You may also reach out to SPN's EU Representative, Shalin Patel at Shalin\_Patel@spe.sony.com, if You have questions or concerns regarding SPN's privacy practices.

Last Updated: 10th August, 2021.

Explore Shows[* SET Shows](https://www.sonyliv.com/listing/set-shows-79421_12011)[* SAB Shows](https://www.sonyliv.com/listing/sab-shows-79421_12013)[* Marathi Shows](https://www.sonyliv.com/listing/marathi-shows-79421_12012)

•3.5.77

© 2024 Sony Pictures Networks India Pvt. Ltd.
